http://www.bazooka.com/privacy

Party Bars Parts & Accessories Bass Tubes®Passive Bass Tubes®Amplified Bass Tubes®MarineAmplifierCoaxialsPassive Bass TubesAmplified Bass TubesTubbiesATV-TubesParts & AccessoriesRemotesCables & Wiring KitsControls & SwitchesMounts & ClampsAmpsWoofersSale
0
Fast Free Same-Day Shipping on Orders Over $50
My Account
0
Search
Home
Privacy
Privacy Policy
Effective Date: 07.06.18
Introduction
Bazooka (“Company”, “us”, “our” or “we”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy (“Privacy Policy”).
This Privacy Policy describes the personal information Bazooka collects about you, and how we use and share that information. This policy applies to personal information we collect when you sign up for Bazooka; access or use our website, products, or services (collectively, the “Services”); or when you otherwise interact with us, including through email, text and other electronic messages. It does not apply to information collected by (i) us offline or through any other means, or (ii) any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from our Services.
This Privacy Policy refers to personal information which is information that can be associated with a specific person and used to identify that person. Personal information does not include information that has been anonymized so that it does not identify a specific user, which may be used for any legal purpose.
This Privacy Policy covers the following topics:
Updates to the Privacy Policy
Sources of Information About You
Our Use of Information
Sharing of Information
Updating Information
Links to Other Websites
Children’s Privacy
Security
Contact Information
Effective Date
Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Services. By accessing or using our Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy.
Updates to the Privacy Policy
We may update, amend, revise or otherwise change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by posting the updated policy and revising the “Effective Date” above. Your continued use of the Services constitutes your acceptance of the then-effective Privacy Policy.
Sources of Information About You
We obtain information about you from a variety of sources, including you, your interaction with Bazooka, and third parties. Such information may include your name, postal address, email address, and telephone number, among other personally identifiable information.
Information you provide to us: If you use certain Services, you may be required to provide us certain information.
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Services, subscribing to our Services, posting material or requesting further services
We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Services
Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us
Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes
Details of transactions you carry out through our Services and of the fulfillment of your orders
Your search queries on our website or through our Services
Information we collect from your use of the Services and other interactions you have with Bazooka:
We may collect your usage information about how you use the Services, including your access times, location, browser types and language, and Internet Protocol addresses. We may collect device-specific information when you access our Services, including your hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, mobile network information, and information about the device's interaction with our Services.
The information we collect automatically is statistical data and may or may not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve and to deliver better and more personalized Services, including by enabling us to:
·           Estimate our audience size and usage patterns
·           Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Services according to your individual interests
·           Speed up your searches
·           Recognize you when you return to our Services
The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:
·           Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Services. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Services
·           Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Services may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Services. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies
·           Web Beacons. Pages of the Services or our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit Bazooka, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity)
Our Use of Information
We use information about you to provide, maintain, personalize and improve our Services and to deliver the information and support your requests, including receipts, technical notices, security alerts, and support and administrative messages.
We may use information we collect to send you news and information about our Services and to communicate with you about products, services, contests, promotions, incentives, and rewards offered by us and select partners. You may opt out of receiving promotional emails or text messages from Bazooka by following the instructions in those emails or text messages. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as messages about your account or our ongoing business relations.
We may also use information about you (i) to track and analyze trends and usage in connection with our Services; (ii) to process and deliver contest and promotion entries and rewards; (iii) to protect our rights or property; (iv) to compare information for accuracy; (v) to verify your identity; (vi) to investigate and prevent fraud or other illegal activities; and (vii) for any other purpose disclosed to you in connection with our Services.
Additionally, we use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:
·           To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us
·           To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it
·           To provide you with notices about your account/subscription, including expiration and renewal notices
·           To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection
·           To notify you about changes to our Services or any products or services we offer or provide though them
·           In any other way, we may describe when you provide the information.
·           For any other purpose with your consent
We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements.
We may use third-party service providers to process and store personal information in the United States and other countries.
Sharing of Information
We may share personal information about you as follows:
To our subsidiaries and affiliates
To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them
To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request
To enforce or apply our terms of service, available at https://www.bazooka.com/tandc, and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes
If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Bazooka, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction
To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it
With third parties that run advertising campaigns, contests, special offers, or other events or activities in connection with our Services
For any lawful purpose, including, without limitation, selling your data to third parties
With your consent or direction
We may also share non-personally identifiable information (aggregated or otherwise) with third parties for any reason.
Updating Information
You may update or correct information about yourself by emailing us at [email protected]  or by accessing your “My Account” page.
Rights of European Residents
Some data protection laws, including the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), provide you with certain rights in connection with personal information you have shared with us. If you are resident in the European Economic Area, you may have the following rights:
The right to be informed. You are entitled to be informed of the use of your personal information. This Privacy Policy provides such information to you.
The right of access. You have the right to request a copy of your personal information which we hold about you.
The right of correction: You have the right to request correction or changes of your personal information if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date.
The right to be forgotten: You have the right to request us, at any time, to delete your personal information from our servers and to erase your personal information when it is no longer necessary for us to retain such data. Note, however, that deletion of your personal information will likely impact your ability to use our services.
The right to object (opt-out): You have the right to opt-out of certain uses of your personal information, such as direct marketing, at any time.
The right to data portability: You have the right to a “portable” copy of your personal information that you have submitted to us. Generally, this means your right to request that we move, copy or transmit your personal information stored on our servers / IT environment to another service provider’s servers / IT environment.
The right to refuse to be subjected to automated decision making, including profiling: You have the right not to be subject to a decision and insist on human intervention if the decision is based on automated processing and produces a legal effect or a similarly significant effect on you.
The right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
Links to Other Web Sites; Third Party Applications
Bazooka is not responsible for any practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor their information or content. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another website, this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. Additionally, some content or applications, including advertisements, on or through the Services are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies, alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies, to collect information about you when you use our Services. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content. We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.
Children's Privacy
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act was created to protect children under the age of 13 from unsuspecting acts or practices in conjunction with collecting, using, and disclosing any information about them. Our Services are not intended for anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on or through our Services. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you are a parent or guardian or otherwise believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us so that we can delete the child's information. The Services will never knowingly accept, collect, maintain or use any information from a child under the age of 13. If a child whom we know to be under the age of 13 sends personal information to us online, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child or notify parents.
Security
The safety and security of your personal information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to or through our Services. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on or within the Services.
Contact Information
Please contact us with any questions or concerns regarding our policy at this address:
[email protected]
About Us:
As pioneers of compact, high-quality bass speakers since 1983, we are dedicated to manufacturing the audio gear you love for the ultimate music experience. Founded on innovation, our patented Bass Tubes enclosure is just the starting point for a line of unbeatable audio products.
Customer Services
Shipping Returns Warranty Registration Installation Manuals Wiring Diagrams Patents & Trademarks FAQsSAS Corporate
© 2020 BAZOOKA. All Rights Reserved.
